<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Science Portfolio on AMPONSAH MICHAEL</title>
    <link>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Science Portfolio on AMPONSAH MICHAEL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: A React Blog Application</title>
      <link>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>A blog Application with a Login and Register Page which help authenticate. New user can write a post   Link to GitHub Repository</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Text Clsssification Application</title>
      <link>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>A text data is collected and train to build a model.
  The model was build using BagOfWords, naive_bayes
  A storage database is created using sqlite to store the model built.
  A created Sqlite functions are created to store, retrieve and view the data.
  The built model is then used to predict text as software or hardware.
  The Application has three interface; Home, Manage and About</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: End To End Emotion Classifier</title>
      <link>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>For this example project is a Emotion classifier to predict the emotion from text. This could be useful for someone who is new to NLP from a certain country. A model was build using LogisticRegression pipeline. The model was imported using Joblib and the main application was build using streamlit.
I was able to get the model to predict the emotion of someone text with 62% accuracy after minimal tuning. For most of the cases this would meet the need of an end user of the app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Data Science Enthusiat And React Dev   Data Science and React Dev are my passions. My name is Amponsah Michael and I have been working in the data science field doing a lot of analysis, research and projects for the last 2 years. I see how some people were very far off in their prediction about the current day, but others came very close, and those were the one that inspired me to continue in this field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me on these social media platforms.
   Platform URL     Twitter: https://twitter.com/PLATINI983   LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/amponsah-michael-27237a108/   GitHub: https://github.com/Platini983    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
