<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on AMPONSAH MICHAEL</title>
    <link>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on AMPONSAH MICHAEL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 3: A React Blog Application</title>
      <link>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>The Application was design using functional React components and React Dom. A REST API with MongoDB was created using Node.js. Then A full MERN Stack(MongoDB, Express, React, Node) was created. MongoDB - document database. Express(.js) - Node.js web framework. React(.js) - a client-side JavaScript framework. Node(.js) - the premier JavaScript web server. A full stack blog Application with a Login and Register Page which help authenticate user. New user can write a post and view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Text Clsssification Application</title>
      <link>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>A text data is collected and train to build a model.
  The model was build using BagOfWords, naive_bayes.
  A storage database is created using sqlite to store the model built.
  A created Sqlite functions are created to store, retrieve and view the data.
  The built model is then used to predict text as software or hardware.
  The Application has three interface; Home, Manage and About</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: End To End Emotion Classifier</title>
      <link>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Platini983.github.io/Platini_Portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>For this example project is a Emotion classifier to predict the emotion from text. This could be useful for someone who is new to NLP from a certain country. A model was build using LogisticRegression pipeline. The model was imported using Joblib and the main application was build using streamlit.
I was able to get the model to predict the emotion of someone text with 62% accuracy after minimal tuning. For most of the cases this would meet the need of an end user of the app.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
